Division of Paleobotany Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Maps, Series I
  - Topographic Maps. United States., 000003
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Castle Gardens scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4352.5-W10730/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000638
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Zimmerman Buttes scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4345-10752.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000639
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Vocation scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000645
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Stone Barn Camp scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W109845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000648
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Sheep Canyon scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10807.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000653
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: North Emblem Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10815/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000655
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Orchard Bench scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10800/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000656
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Lovell scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10822.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000662
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Banjo Flats W scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4352.5-W10752.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000665
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Banjo Flats E scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4352.5-W10745/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000666
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Alkali Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10800/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000668
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Corbett Dam scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000674
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Jack Horner Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10822.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000677
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Jones Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10807.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000678
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Gilmore Hill scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000681
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Gilmore Hill NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000682
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Gould Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4422.5-W10807.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000683
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Gilmore Hill NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000685
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Gilmore Hill SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000686
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Emblem SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10815/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000689
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Frannie scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000691
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Henry Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4345-W10745/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000703
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Greybull South scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4422.5-W10800/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000723
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Elk Basin scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-w10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000729
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Garland scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000731
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Elk Basin se scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000732
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Elk Basin NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000733
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Deaver Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W10837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000734
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Elk Basin scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: 44108-H7-TF-024 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000744
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Ralston scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000658
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Emblem scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10822.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000664
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Big Horn scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W106452.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000697
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Buffalo Run Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10645/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000702
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Byron scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000704
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Old Maid Gulch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10715/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000728
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Sheridan scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N445-W10652.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000699
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Wyarno scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10645/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000701
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Warren scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000730
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Jones Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10637.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000698
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Verona scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10637.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000700
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Nowater Creek scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4330-W10800/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000721
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Chimney Gulch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N435230-W1080730/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000705
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Blue Mesa E scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N435230-W10815/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000706
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Meeteetse W scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N440730-w1085230/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000707
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Little Buffalo Basin scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000711
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Meeteetse E. scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N440730-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000712
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hamilton Dome scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4345-W10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000714
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Iron Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W1085230/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000715
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Neiber scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N435230-W10800/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000716
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Little Sand Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4245-W10815 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000717
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Blue Mesa scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N435230-W1082230 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1985; 000718
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Chapman Bench scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W1090730/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1987; 000708
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: North Bennett Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N445230-10915/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1987; 000710
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Clark scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N445230-W1090730 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1987; 000713
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Cody scale: 1:100 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W11000/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1987; 000719
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Badland Hills scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10900/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1987; 000740
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Badland Hills scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10900/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1987; 000741
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Worland scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10800/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1989; 000722
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Bald Peak scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10915/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1991; 000709
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Basin scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10900/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1992; 000720
    - Wyoming`. Quadrangle: Elk Basin SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N445-W10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000757
  - Topographic Maps. International., 000004
    - Canada. Quadrangle: Waterton Lakes Park scale: 1:63360 Latitude/Longtitude: N4900-W11410 Publisher: Canada Mines and Technical Surveys, 1928; 000016
    - Canada. Quadrangle: Jasper Park scale: 1:190 080 Latitude/Longtitude: N5215-W11830/ Publisher: Canada Mines and Technical Surveys, 1936; 000014
    - Canada. Quadrangle: Banff Park Alberta scale: 1:190 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N5154-W11715 Publisher: Canada Mines and Technical Surveys, 1955; 000013
    - Canada. Quadrangle: Jasper Park scale: 1:190 080 Latitude/Longtitude: N5251-W11811/ Publisher: Canada Mines and Technical Surveys, 1956; 000015
- Field Notes, Series II
  Field notes of various collectors.
  - Becker, Herman F. Beaverhead Basins., 001059
  - Delevoryas, Theodore. Locality record., 001058
  - Hickey, Leo J. & D.W. Taylor. Locality/Field Notes. Jurassic, England., 1992; 001050
  - Horton, J. O. Dissertation/Locality Information. Piney Formation, Wyoming., 1934; 001048
  - McClammer, James U. Locality/Field Notes. San Juan Basin, New Mexico., 1981-1984; 001052
  - McClammer, James U. Locality/Field Notes. Pakistan., Dec 1981 - Jan 1982.; 001051
  - Miller, Ian M. Locality/Field Notes. Winthrop Formation, Washington., 2002-2003; 001053
  - Smith, Una. Locality/Field Notes. Denver Basin. Paleoaster Localities., 001054
  - Tamm, Valerie. Dissertation/Locality Information, Fort Union Formation, Montana., 1989; 001046
  - Van Boskirk, Martin C. Locality/Field Notes. Eagle Formation, Elk Basin, Park County, Wyoming., 1995-1996; 001056
  - Waage, Karl M. Locality notes, records, etc., 001055
  - Wieland, George R. Field notebook., 1909; 001043
  - Williams, Beth. Dissertation/Locality Information, Paleocene River System, Montana., 1988; 001047
- Princeton & New York Botanical Gardens Related Archives, Series III
  Archives relating to the aquisition of the Princeton and New York Botanical Garden collections.
  - Dorf, Erling. Pictures, notes, etc. Relating to Princeton Collection., 001037
  - New York Botanical Garden. Catalogs of the NYBG., 001039
- Researchers, affiliates, etc., Series IV
  Archives related to individual researchers, affiliates, etc.
  - Erling Dorf Archives., 001066
    - Erling Dorf Archives. MS. Early Tertiary Fossil Forests., 1959; 001068
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Summer Plans, 1966; 001070
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Redmond Mine Flora, Labrador., 001049
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Idaho Paper, 001067
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Ginko Paper., 001069
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Photographs - NY Pleistocene Leaves., 001071
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Original Plates., 001072
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Bear Creek Flora, Montana., 001073
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Hickey Cretaceaous-Tertiary Boundary, 001074
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Golden Valley Flora, 001075
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Green River Floras, 001076
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Drawings by Judy Knight, 001077
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Tatman Flora., 001078
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Beaverhead Flora, 001079
    - Erling Dorf Archives. MS Plates., 001080
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Valley Ranch Flora, 001081
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Kootenai Flora, 001082
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Wildwood Flora, 001083
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Wildwood Flora, 001084
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Wildwood Flora, 001085
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Valley Ranch Flora, 001086
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Pliocene Floras of California. Original Plates., 001087
    - Erling Dorf Archives. Notes on Revision of Lance Flora., 001088
- Miscellaneous, Series V
  Miscellaneous archives.
  - Heer, Oswald. Flora Fossilis Arctica, Vol. 2, No. 2-4., 1870; 001045
  - Heer, Oswald. Unbound Flora Fossils, Vol. 1-7., 001044
  - Inventories. Inventories of the collections. Two black 3-ring binders., 001035
  - Martha's Vineyard. Martha's Vineyard localities., 001057
  - Stiles Clay Pit. Correspondence, pictures, negatives, notes, figures etc. relating to the Stiles Clay Pit., 001042
  - USNM. Records of USNM Plant types., 001040
  - USNM. Records of Princeton Specimens at the USNM., 001041
  - USNM. USNM locality numbers., 001060
- Compendium Index, Series VI
  - Algae, Fungi, and Others., 001064
  - Angiosperms., 001062
  - Gymnosperms., 001063
- Ledgers & Card Catalogs., Series VII
- George Wieland Archives, Series VIII
  - American Fossil Cycads., 001104
    - Wieland, George R. 1906. American fossil Cycads, vol. I, Structure. Carnegie Institution of Washington Publication. 34: 1-296. (also as publication record PB.00055), 001102
  - Miscellaneous; American Fossil Cycads., 001110
    - Negative and Print. Wieland negative and print, Miscellaneous picture, 001540
    - Negative and Prints. Wieland negative and prints, Miscellaneous picture, Prints x3, 001542
    - Negatives and Prints. Wieland negative and print, Miscellaneous picture, 001430
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 98, fig 5c, 001224
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 18, fig 4; C. dacotensis, 001225
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Text support B, fig 6, 001226
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 20, fig 6, 001227
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Isle of Wight, Plate 20, fig 2, 001229
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 19, fig 1, 001230
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 19, fig 1, 001231
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 12, fig 3; Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001232
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 18, fig 4, 001233
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 20, fig 3, 001234
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 29, fig 1; Isle of Wight; Bennettites scotti, 001235
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, House, 001236
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, House, 001237
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Drawing, 001238
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001239
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001240
    - Negatives. Cryptozoon, 001241
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001242
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Plate 12, fig 5; Raumeria reichenbachiona, an end-to-end print, 001243
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Plate 12, fig 5; Raumelia reichonbachiona, 001244
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001245
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001246
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001247
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001248
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001249
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001250
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001251
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001252
    - Negatives. Enecphalartas, 001253
    - Negatives. Encephalartas, 001254
    - Negatives. Cycadeoid wood structure, 001255
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea painei, 001256
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001257
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea: longitudinal section of Strobili, 001258
    - Negatives. Caytonia sewardi fruit, 001259
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea sp., 001260
    - Negatives. Cordaites principalis, 001261
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea: longitudinal section of Strobili, 001262
    - Negatives. Coratozamia mexicana, 001263
    - Negatives. Raumoria reichenbachia, pal., 001264
    - Negatives. Stangeria paradoxa, 001265
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea: longitudinal section of Strobili, 001266
    - Negatives. Stangeria, 001267
    - Negatives. Sphaerostoma ovule, 001268
    - Negatives. Cycas circinalis, 001269
    - Negatives. Cycas circinalis, 001270
    - Negatives. Hyrbrid: Ceratozamia and Zamia, 001271
    - Negatives. Zamia floridana, 001272
    - Negatives. Cordaites principalis, 001273
    - Negatives. C. painei, 001274
    - Negatives. Sage palm, Ceylon, 001275
    - Negatives. Photo of Wieland in Wyoming, 001276
    - Negatives. Cycatheca princeps, 001277
    - Negatives. Calamites communis wood section, 001278
    - Negatives. Evolution of strobilus in cycads, 001279
    - Negatives. Equistem and Archeocalamites bundles, 001280
    - Negatives. Rhatic leaves, 001281
    - Negatives. Rhatic leaves, 001282
    - Negatives. Lycopsida and Pteropsida, 001283
    - Negatives. Archelon, 001284
    - Negatives. Archelon, 001285
    - Negatives. Fossil wood; Squankum, New Jersey; Feb. 24, 1936 (x50), 001286
    - Negatives. Dioon edule, 001287
    - Negatives. Dioon edule, 001288
    - Negatives. Cycad from N.Y. Botanical Garden, 001289
    - Negatives. Ben. gibsonianus, 001290
    - Negatives. Macrozamia, 001291
    - Negatives. Macrozamia spiralis, 001292
    - Negatives. Macrozamia moorei, 001293
    - Negatives. Microcyca calocoma, 001294
    - Negatives. Pollen grains x50, April 30, 1934, 001295
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001296
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001297
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, fig 1a-5, 001298
    - Negatives. Lethaea palaeozoica, Taf 65, fig 1-9, 001299
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001300
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001301
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001302
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001303
    - Negatives. Lepidodendron, 001304
    - Negatives. US Geological Survey, Professional paper No. 35, Plate 3: Fossils of the Perry Formation, 001305
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001306
    - Negatives. Calamodendron commune, 001307
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001308
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001309
    - Negatives. Odontopteris-Wedels, 001310
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001311
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001312
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001313
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001314
    - Negatives. American Journal of Science: Vol. 240, March 1942; C. minuta, 001322
    - Negatives. American Journal of Science: Vol. 240, March 1942; C. minuta, 001323
    - Negatives. Bariera argentine Kurtz; Shells and insect wing, Nov. 17, 1925, 001324
    - Negatives. Bennottites gibsonianus, 001325
    - Negatives. Cycadella-like, 001326
    - Negatives. Proacroncaria mirablis, Cerro Cuadrado Petrified Forest, Plate 7, figure 3, 001327
    - Negatives. A. imbricata, 001330
    - Negatives. B. gibsonianus, 001331
    - Negatives. Wieland negative; Metallographic plate, green rayfilter, microtessar 32 stopped down, 001332
    - Negatives. Drimys winteri, 001333
    - Negatives. Wieland negative; Metallographic plate without rayfilter, Obj. 3 Oc. 4; Transmitted light with aplauatic substage at brightest incandescant ribbon light. Expose 30 seconds, 001334
    - Negatives. C. etrusca, 001335
    - Negatives. Wieland negatives, Miscellaneous picture, 001336
    - Negatives. Trochodendron, 001337
    - Negatives. B. gibsonianus x100, 001338
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001339
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001340
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001341
    - Negatives. Dictyophyllum exile, 001342
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001343
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001344
    - Negatives. Trochodendron, 001345
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001346
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001347
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001348
    - Negatives. Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001349
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea paineii, Cambium, Cerro Cuadrado, Plate 14, fig. 5, 001354
    - Negatives. Fossil Cycads, with Special Reference to Raumeria Reichenbachiana Goeppert Sp. of the Zwinger Dresden; Plate 16, fig 5, Cycadeoidea paynei (type), 001355
    - Negatives. Fossil Cycads, with Special Reference to Raumeria Reichenbachiana Goeppert Sp. of the Zwinger Dresden; Plate 17, fig 1, Cycadeoidea painei, 001356
    - Negatives. Fossil Cycads, with Special Reference to Raumeria Reichenbachiana Goeppert Sp. of the Zwinger Dresden; Isle of Wright fronds, Plate 20, fig 1, Cycadeoidea scotti, 001357
    - Negatives. Fossil Cycads, with Special Reference to Raumeria Reichenbachiana Goeppert Sp. of the Zwinger Dresden; Frond, Plate 20, fig 3, Cycadeoidea scotti, 001358
    - Negatives. Fossil Cycads, with Special Reference to Raumeria Reichenbachiana Goeppert Sp. of the Zwinger Dresden; Frond; Similar to figures on Plate 20, Cycadeoidea scotti, 001359
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 2, fig 1; Raumeria, 001373
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 12, fig 3; Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001374
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 12, fig 4; Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001375
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 12, fig 6; Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001376
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 14; Raumeria, 001377
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 13, fig 1; Pollen grains x125, 001378
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 13, fig 1a; Pollen grains x400, 001379
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 14, fig 2; Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001380
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 15, fig 2; Raumeria, 001381
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica; Plate 17, fig 4; Cycadeoidea painei, 001382
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Plate 17, fig 4; D. winteri x100, 001383
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Plate 17, fig 4; Cycadeoidea painei, 001384